panoramastock.com 2007-05-30

# PanoramaMedia

|  |   
---  
|   Privacy|   
|   
---  
  
Panorama Media respects your right to privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our practices with regards to any personal information we collect online. **Use of Personal Information**  
When you visit our website, we may require you to provide us with certain information. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, VAT number and credit card number. This information will be used for internal purposes only and more particularly to fulfil licensing transactions, download images, send you products and updates on our latest promotions and services. We may also use certain account information provided to us by authorized users to conduct credit inquiries. age fotostock does not sell or lease information about its customers to third parties.   
By making this information available to Panorama Media you are agreeing to allow us to share this information with Panorama Media's partners, subsidiaries, affiliates, any third party content provider, necessary payment processors or third parties which services are required to carry out your order. We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in order to comply with any legal process.   
Providing information to us is always voluntary, and you are free not to complete any online forms. If you choose not to, however some products or services may not be available to you.   
In accordance with Chinese legislation relating to the Protection of Privacy regarding personal data processing (LOPD), you may, at anytime, access, correct, update or require us to unsubscribe you from our mailing list by sending us an e-mail at [Jessie@panoramastock.com](mailto:Jessie@panoramastock.com) **Security**   
Panorama Media recognizes your concern for security and will use all reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with you and protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts information you input. However be aware that perfect security on the Internet does not exist.   
Only authorized employees have access to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our service. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort (such as use of employee passwords) to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. **Use of cookies**   
When you visitage Panorama Media website, we place a "cookie" in the hard drive of your computer. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that a website can store on your web browser and later retrieve. Cookies allow age fotostock to make its website more useful by storing information about your preferences. For example, cookies enable this website to recognize the information you have consented to give us, such as the lightboxes you have created and determine what areas of the website are most of your interest. You can set your browser's option not to accept cookies, though as a result you may not then be able to access all of the features of age fotostock site. **Links**   
Please be aware that the age fotostock web site may contain links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. i Panorama Media's not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We recommend that you read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. **Changes of PanoramaStock 's Online Privacy Policy**   
PanoramaStock reserves the right to change its online privacy policy at any time but will not do so without posting the revised policy on this website.   
If you have any questions about Panorama Media privacy policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied, please contact us at toll free number85212933(only for Beijing)
